greataupair.com 2018-10-11

# Nanny Agency Au Pair Work Child Care Jobs Babysitter Service

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to www.GreatAuPair.com and www.GreatAuPairUSA.com which are owned and operated by GreatAuPair, LLC (GreatAuPair). As part of our Terms of Use, your explicit consent to this privacy policy is required upon registration. This privacy policy describes how GreatAuPair collects and uses the personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit on our websites. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personally identifiable information and how you can access, update or remove your information from our websites.

It is GreatAuPair's policy to maintain strict security and privacy practices to protect its systems and its customer data. GreatAuPair maintains compliance with U.S. State and Federal laws, as well as the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) for EU residents, effective May 25, 2018. Please visit our Security Center to learn more about how we help protect you and how you can help protect yourself against potential online fraud.

### Anti-Spam & UCE Policy

GreatAuPair does not send out unsolicited commercial emails or any form of spam. Please read our Unsolicited Commercial Email Policy to see what you can do to correctly identify spammers and put an end to their emails. If you have received what you believe to be spam, you may have received a spoofed email with forged headers. Learn how to identify phishing scams and emails.

### GDPR Compliance

GreatAuPair complies with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) as applicable. Similar to existing legal requirements, compliance with the GDPR requires a partnership between GreatAuPair and its customers in their use of our services. We are also dedicated to helping our customers comply with the GDPR. GreatAuPair has a firm commitment to safeguarding the privacy of its members' Personally Identifiable Information. Some of the ways in which we ensure data and privacy protection in compliance with the GDPR are through:

  * Access controls
  * Roles-based privileges
  * Enhanced data security
  * Data obfuscation
  * Data encryption
  * Data audits or assessments
  * Data subject request procedures
  * Staff training on security and data protection
  * Contractual agreements with staff and agents

### Privacy & Personally Identifiable Information

We collect personally identifiable information when you voluntarily submit it to us, such as first and last name, birthdate, email address, a home, postal or other physical address or phone number during the registration and payment processes and, occasionally, at other times.

Similarly, if you contact us through our website to inquire about employment opportunities with GreatAuPair, we may collect and store the information you provide for recruiting purposes. On our Job Opportunities pages, you may be asked for information necessary for the recruiting process such as your name, address, phone and other contact information, along with your photo, resume and cover letter. Before you can submit your résumé and cover Letter you must explicitly consent to the following uses of your résumé, cover letter and any personally identifiable information you provide to GreatAuPair: (1) GreatAuPair its affiliates, and agents will store, access, and use the information you provide in any jurisdiction, including jurisdictions whose privacy laws may be different and less protective than those of your home jurisdiction; and (2) GreatAuPair, its affiliates and agents, may use this information to evaluate your eligibility for employment and to contact you for recruiting purposes. Please note that people under 18 years old are not authorized to submit recruiting information.

Information collected by GreatAuPair is securely stored by physical and electronic means. Data collected by GreatAuPair will be shared with third parties only in ways that are described in this privacy policy and will not be sold or rented on an individual basis to independent third parties without your knowledge or permission. By accepting the GreatAuPair Terms of Use, you acknowledge and grant permission to GreatAuPair to use your Personal Contact Information as specifically stated under Uses of Personal Contact Information, herein, through GreatAuPair's services and its websites.

Search engines may index publicly available information from your profile, such as your first name, your city, and other public data that is searchable by anyone on the Internet. Search engines do not have access to any Personal Contact Information contained within the fields of a profile, some of which is available only to paid members of the GreatAuPair service. Personal Contact Information is defined as first and last name together, email address, phone number and physical street address. We also collect your credit card number and related billing information if you make a purchase. With your permission, we will also supplement data through a background check as needed to satisfy U.S. Department of State Au Pair Program Requirements and or for pre-employment screening.

### Uses of Personal Contact Information

Paid members may see your first and last name listed on your profile. You have the option of providing your phone number, which you may elect to display or not display to paid members; either families or care providers who are claiming to seek a working relationship with you as a result of your online registration. Your email address is not visible to anyone, except to those whom you directly send an email during the time you have a paid subscription. Your physical address is not revealed on the website. A map showing the location of your city or zip code is available and may be seen by registered users. No representations or warranties are made regarding the legitimacy of the claims of those who have paid for a membership subscription to contact you through GreatAuPair's private messaging system which relies on your Personal Contact Information. You are urged to validate the identity of anyone who contacts you and utilize the background check resources available to you through the GreatAuPair service before making any commitments or arrangements. We do not sell, share, rent or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

The information you provide during registration may also be used to enable us to process, validate and verify services or membership subscription purchases. We may also provide advertisers with aggregate - never individual - information about our member base and usage patterns. We may also use aggregated information to develop new features and services to better meet member needs.

Internally we may use aggregated and personally identifiable information to improve our marketing efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings as well as to customize our site's content and layout. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor your online experience to meet your needs.

We also may use personally identifiable information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as GreatAuPair services, news, updates, promotions, Favorites notifications or FastMatch emails. You may opt out of receiving such automated information services at any time by signing in to your account: click My Account then click the Account Options link to modify your privacy and communications preferences.

Users also may post third-party personally identifiable information, such as name and email for referral purposes. This information is used only for the purposes which it was collected.

We use personally identifiable information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms of Use, which may include providing your information to government and law enforcement officials as required by law.

### Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, deactivate or delete it by making your desired changes on your My Account page or by contacting our Customer Support team by email, phone or U.S. mail.

### Communications from the Site

As part of your registration and your acceptance of our Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, you are agreeing to receive emails from GreatAuPair and its members. While you may opt out from receiving certain types of emails such as Favorite Notifications or FastMatch emails, you may cease all emails from the site and its members by deactivating your profile or canceling your account. To deactivate your profile or cancel your account, sign in and click My Account and select your desired options under Account Options. When your account is deactivated or canceled, you will receive an email confirming such action. To remove unauthorized profiles, please send an email to Customer Support.

We reserve the right to contact any member at any time regarding subscription renewals, profile deactivation, account cancellation, subject data requests and other membership-related problems or questions.

### Special Offers and Updates

We will occasionally send you information on special services or promotions. You may receive these emails from us as part of your registration.

Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. At the bottom of every Special Offer email, you will find an "Opt-out" link at the bottom, which if clicked, will remove your name from the list of recipients for future mailings of that type.

### Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. At the bottom of every Newsletter, you will find an "Opt-out" link at the bottom, which if clicked, will remove your name from the list of recipients for future Newsletters.

### Service-related Announcements

We will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate or cancel your account.

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information to enforce our Terms of Use, prevent fraud, or as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. If GreatAuPair is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information.

### Links to Other Sites

This website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by GreatAuPair. Please be aware that we, GreatAuPair, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy policy applies only to information collected by GreatAuPair and its websites.

If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. To request removal of your personally identifiable information from our bulletin board or chat room, contact us at Customer Support. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

We also have testimonials and reviews on our sites, for which users have given permission to have their personally identifiable information posted on our sites. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at Customer Support.

### Security

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number, driver's license number, national ID number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using industry standard encrption and transmission methods such as SHA256 or AES and/or secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about how we help protect you and your privacy, visit our Security Center. 

### Tell-A-Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. GreatAuPair does not store and only uses this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

### Agents/Service Providers

We use third parties such as a credit card processing company to bill you for services. When you sign up for our service, we will share only that specific personally identifiable information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for promotional purposes.

### Widgets

Our website includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. allowing you to share a profile with your Facebook or Twitter account). Personally identifiable information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

### Control of Your Password

You may not disclose your password to any third parties or share it with any third parties. If, despite the foregoing, you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.

### Research

We also may conduct occasional online surveys. If you choose to participate, you'll be prompted to answer a series of online questions. Your responses are confidential and will be used for statistical analysis only; no information on an individual's preferences will be shared with any outside organization without your permission.

### Tracking Technologies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by GreatAuPair and our marketing and analytics partners. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user's movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies to help members move faster through our site and recall certain perferences automatically. When a member signs on to GreatAuPair we may pass a cookie to that user's computer. A cookie is a string of information that's sent by a website and stored on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer's memory. This avoids the potentially time-consuming task of entering your user name and password each time a page is requested. Data contained in the cookies is encrypted and is not linked to personally identifiable information. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

Click here to learn more about cookies and how we use them on this site.

### Advertising

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### Local Storage

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store session content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 or Flash to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>.

### Log Files

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, browser version, internet service provider (ISP), ISP region, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you and site functionality.

### Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact our Customer Support team by email, phone or U.S. mail. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Changes in this Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here or by email prior to the change becoming effective.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact our support team via the support ticketing system or via U.S. Mail at 12600 Hill Country Blvd, Suite R-275, Austin, TX 78738.

GreatAuPair may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, so please check back periodically. Last updated April 6th, 2018.
